[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the process of dispersing milk fat throughout the milk?", "correct_answer": "Homogenization", "incorrect_answers": ["Pasteurization", "Fortification", "Ultrapasteurization"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the currency of Russia?", "correct_answer": "ruble", "incorrect_answers": ["franc", "dollar", "peso"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the long-suffering character from the Bibles Old Testament?", "correct_answer": "Job", "incorrect_answers": ["Zeb", "Set", "Uri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors said How do you like your ribs??", "correct_answer": "Carl Weathers in Action Jackson", "incorrect_answers": ["Nick Nolte in Another 48 Hours", "Dolph Lundgren in Rocky IV", "Mel Gibson in Lethal Weapon II"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who starred as Marshall Will Kane in High Noon?", "correct_answer": "Gary Cooper", "incorrect_answers": ["John Wayne", "James Arness", "Clark Gable"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Academy Award nominations did the 2001 movie The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring receive?", "correct_answer": "Thirteen", "incorrect_answers": ["Ten", "Fifteen", "Eight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The portrayal of what Shakespearean character brought Laurence Olivier an Academy Award for Best Actor in 1948?", "correct_answer": "Hamlet", "incorrect_answers": ["Othello", "Henry V", "Romeo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Once occupied by the Romans and then later the Vikings, which Yorkshire city is said to be the most haunted in Europe if not the world?", "correct_answer": "York", "incorrect_answers": ["Kingston upon Hull", "Ripon", "Leeds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The best diet is a permanent lifestyle change.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bobby Leach, a circus stuntman from Cornwell, England, famous for surviving a barrel ride over the Niagara Falls, died in what way?", "correct_answer": "He slipped on a orange peel and died.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was one of the first casualties of WWI.", "He died during an attempt to swim the English Channel.", "In 1912 he was aboard the Titanic and drowned."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Topic: Childrens Books. This series, written by Marc Brown, stars this bespectacled aardvark. What is the right question?", "correct_answer": "Who is Arthur?", "incorrect_answers": ["Who is Junie B. Jones?", "Who is Captain Underpants?", "Who is Curious George?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The poles of magnets are able to point the way because of ferromagnetic materials deep inside the Earth\u2019s core.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]